<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FluBot Malware Uninstall</string>
    <string name="showSetAsLauncher_text">Please tap on the button to set this tool as your default launcher. If asked repeatedly, choose "Always". This step will be undone after the removal of the malware.</string>
    <string name="showSetAsLauncher_button">Set as launcher</string>

    <string name="showBeginUninstall_text">Please take into account this may remove WeChat if you had it previously installed. If you are asked to choose a launcher, choose "Always" option for FluBot Malware Uninstall. Ignore the error messages and proceed to uninstall the malware by tapping on "OK" when requested.</string>
    <string name="showBeginUninstall_button">Uninstall malware</string>

    <string name="showRemoveDefaultLauncher_text">Please tap on the button to choose back your default application launcher. Do not choose FluBot Malware Uninstall.</string>
    <string name="showRemoveDefaultLauncher_button">Tap to choose your launcher</string>

    <string name="showNotFound_text">No known FluBot malware application was found on your device</string>
    <string name="showNotFound_button">Malware not found</string>

    <string name="alternativeFlowStart_text">The malware is not uninstalled yet. Let\'s try something else. After tapping on the button above, you will be prompted to choose your launcher again. This time, do not choose \"Always\" and do not tick any \"Remember selection\" option.</string>
    <string name="alternativeFlowStart_button">Start alternative solution</string>

    <string name="alternativeFlow_text">Great, now after you tap on the Uninstall button above, you will be prompted to choose your launcher again. This time, do not choose any of them, but close the menu by pressing the back key, or simply touch anywhere else in the screen. Afterwards, you will be able to uninstall the malware by tapping on "OK" several times in a row when requested.</string>
    <string name="alternativeFlow_button">Uninstall with alternative method</string>
    <string name="alternativeFlow_toast">Press the back button or tap anywhere else on the screen now</string>

    <string name="error_text">Something went wrong</string>
    <string name="success_text">Malware removed</string>
</resources>